http://www.hegel.com/privacy-policy

How we use your information
This privacy policy relates to our online services available via our website at www.hegel.com and any of our other online or mobile products, content and services from time to time. This privacy policy addresses information provided to Hegel Music Systems. In the event that Hegel Music Systems engages with a third-party service provider, to whom we may pass your personal information or to whom you may be expected to provide your personal information, your information will be handled by that third-party service provider as if it were being handled by Hegel Music Systems. This may include but not be limited to external training organizations, external auditing organizations, external certification organizations, external personnel benefits advisers and statutory authorities. Exceptions to this arrangement are specifically stated within this privacy policy. By using the service, you consent to the collection, storage and use of your personal information as described below. You do not need to submit any of your personal information when browsing our websites. If you do not agree to this privacy policy, please do not use the service.
Data protection compliance
The service is controlled by us from our offices in Norway. Personal information collected from the service is processed in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation, which regulates the processing of personal data. We comply with GDPR data protection and privacy laws. If you choose to use the service from outside Norway, you do so at your own risk, with the understanding that personal information collected from the service may be collected, stored and used in a country whose privacy laws may be different and less protective than those of your home country.
Information collected
We don't collect personal information, which means data from which you can be identified, including your name, email address and postal address. For safety reasons, our website uses a protection system which blocks IP numbers used by spambots and hackers, but it doesn't collect any personal data from our users as such. For quality control and training purposes, we may also monitor or record your communications with us. On occasion, we may ask for feedback from you about the usage or services our website provides to help us develop and improve it further. We process personal information collected via this website and our telephone lines for the purposes of providing and personalising our services, including customer care, warranty protection and technical or service support, dealing with your inquiries and requests, maintaining information as a reference tool or general resource so that we may improve our products and services for you, and provide you with information about our company, new products, and services or product upgrades. We will keep your information for as long as is reasonably necessary for these purposes. Our website may contain links to other websites which are outside our control and are not covered by this privacy policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours.
Use of cookies
A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information from the browser. Cookies are used for a variety of things that help improve your online experience. These files make the page load quickly by sharing the workload across computers and make sure our page is optimized for your browser or device by giving us technical information about the device or browser you are using. Allowing the use of cookies is recommended, but if you are still not sure, here are some questions and answers about cookies. We use cookies to identify you when you visit this website and to keep track of your browsing patterns and build up a demographic profile. Our use of cookies also allows registered users to be presented with a personalized version of the site, carry out transactions and have access to information about their account. Most browsers allow you to turn off cookies or to receive a warning before a cookie is stored on your hard drive. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about how to do this. However, should you decide to disable any cookies we place on your computer you may not be able to use certain services or facilities on the website. Switching off cookies will restrict your use of our website.
Your rights
You can choose to disable cookies by turning them off in the settings of your web browser. If you have any concerns about the usage of your data, you can also leave our website. However, just by entering our website and using it normally, you don't provide us with any personal information. All the records of traffic and user actions on this website are collected for statistical, marketing and strategic development purposes only. Also, we don't share any of this information with anyone else. However, if you have any questions or doubts regarding your personal information, you can contact us and we will be happy to explain everything to you. If you decide to contact us, please be aware that the act of doing so means you have provided us with some information including your email or anything you decide to share with us in that message. Under the General Data Protection Regulation, you have rights as an individual which you can exercise in relation to the information we hold about you. You may opt-out of receiving information about our products and services by selecting the relevant option on our website or by sending us an email at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it..
Changes to this privacy notice
We keep our privacy notice under regular review. This notice was updated on 22th May 2019.
Our Products
Integrated AmplifiersPreamplifiersPower AmplifiersCustom InstallationD/A ConvertersCD PlayersXtrasDiscontinued
Hegel Technology
Organic SoundSoundEngineDualAmpDualPowerLineDriverMasterClockSynchroDACUSB
Useful Links
HomeSearchPrivacy PolicyPress PackContact usDealer Login
Cookie Info
Our website uses cookies to ensure you have the best experience. By using it you consent to the use of cookies in accordance with your browser's settings. Please see our Privacy Policy for more information.
AboutPeople of HegelProductsIntegratedH90H95H120H190H390H590PreP20P30PowerH20H30CustomC53C54C55DACHD30CDMohicanXtrasDiscontinuedH70H80RöstH100H160H200H300H360H4SESUPERHD12HD25CDP2A MK2CDP4ATechnologyOrganic SoundSoundEngineDualAmpDualPowerLineDriverMasterClockSynchroDACUSBDistributorsEuropeAsiaAmericasOceaniaNewsSupport
